<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<announcements>
		<ID>
			<label>ID</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The ID field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The ID field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The ID field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</ID>
		<TITLE>
			<label>TITLE</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>50</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The TITLE field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The TITLE field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The TITLE field is too long.  This field must be no more than 50 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</TITLE>
		<BODY>
			<label>BODY</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>2000</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The BODY field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The BODY field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The BODY field is too long.  This field must be no more than 2000 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</BODY>
		<PROJECTIDFK>
			<label>PROJECTIDFK</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The PROJECTIDFK field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The PROJECTIDFK field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The PROJECTIDFK field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</PROJECTIDFK>
		<USERIDFK>
			<label>USERIDFK</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The USERIDFK field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The USERIDFK field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The USERIDFK field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</USERIDFK>
		<POSTED>
			<label>POSTED</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>26</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The POSTED field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The POSTED field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The POSTED field is too long.  This field must be no more than 26 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</POSTED>
	</announcements>
