<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<issue>
		<applicationid>
			<label>applicationid</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The applicationid field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The applicationid field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The applicationid field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</applicationid>
		<Id>
			<label>Id</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The Id field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The Id field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The Id field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</Id>
		<name>
			<label>name</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The name field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The name field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The name field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</name>
		<projectidfk>
			<label>projectidfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The projectidfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The projectidfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The projectidfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</projectidfk>
		<created>
			<label>created</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The created field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The created field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</created>
		<updated>
			<label>updated</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The updated field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The updated field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</updated>
		<useridfk>
			<label>useridfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The useridfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The useridfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The useridfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</useridfk>
		<creatoridfk>
			<label>creatoridfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The creatoridfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The creatoridfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</creatoridfk>
		<description>
			<label>description</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65537</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The description field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The description field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The description field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65537 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</description>
		<history>
			<label>history</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65537</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The history field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The history field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The history field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65537 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</history>
		<issuetypeidfk>
			<label>issuetypeidfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The issuetypeidfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The issuetypeidfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The issuetypeidfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</issuetypeidfk>
		<locusidfk>
			<label>locusidfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The locusidfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The locusidfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The locusidfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</locusidfk>
		<severityidfk>
			<label>severityidfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The severityidfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The severityidfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The severityidfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</severityidfk>
		<statusidfk>
			<label>statusidfk</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>35</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The statusidfk field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The statusidfk field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The statusidfk field is too long.  This field must be no more than 35 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</statusidfk>
		<relatedURL>
			<label>relatedURL</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The relatedURL field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The relatedURL field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</relatedURL>
		<attachment>
			<label>attachment</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>255</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The attachment field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The attachment field is too long.  This field must be no more than 255 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</attachment>
		<publicid>
			<label>publicid</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>11</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The publicid field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The publicid field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The publicid field is too long.  This field must be no more than 11 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</publicid>
		<duedate>
			<label>duedate</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The duedate field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</duedate>
	</issue>
